EPISODE 1
I should be arriving in about an hour.
Yes, I understand.
What the hell?
Are you all right?
I was on my phone
and wasn't watching where I was going.
This is absurd.
What?
What did you just say?
Don't worry, he wasn't talking to you.
And who are--
You should be clearer about
who you're talking to, sir.
-She misunderstood--
-Can you believe this ad?
You can hardly tell
what product they're promoting.
They've only slapped
some nameless celebrity on it.
You're right.
I've never seen that guy before.
Find out who was in charge
of this ad immediately.
BASED ON WEBNOVEL AND WEBTOON
A BUSINESS PROPOSAL
Yes, sir.
PREMIUM DUMPLINGS
DELICIOUS DUMPLINGS MADE WITH CAREFULLY
SELECTED PREMIUM INGREDIENTS
"DO YOU WANT TO EAT WITH ME?"
APPLE EXTRACT
SHIN HA-RI
Yes, Ms. Yeo. Oh, already?
Yes, I'm on my way. Okay.
Coming through.
-Ms. Yeo.
-What's this smell?
-Hey.
-Why are you so late?
Because of the mackerel.
Take it easy, will you?
You stink of fish.
Is it that bad? I can't really tell.
How could you not? Come here.
It's fine. It's just proof of
how hard you're working as a researcher.
INAUGURATION OF PRESIDENT KANG TAE-MOO
The inauguration will start soon.
Please be seated.
-Let's go sit.
-Okay.
-Hello.
-This is our new hire, Hye-ji.
Anyway, looks like the rumors are true.
President Kang's quite the workaholic.
He's starting work
on the day he came back to Korea.
I heard he's really hot.
Who knows? He wasn't here when I joined
the company, so I never saw him.
But look at the chairman.
How hot could the grandson be?
It's been a long time coming.
-So the rumors aren't true.
-No.
He's really handsome.
He looks like a celebrity.
Please. The apple doesn’t fall far
from the tree, you know.
President Kang will now make
his inauguration address.
There he is.
He's super hot!
That's…
-Hello, everyone.
-Why is he…
I am Chief Secretary Cha Sung-hoon,
here on behalf of President Kang.
What's going on?
The chief secretary?
I will now deliver
his inauguration address.
What is this…
"Thank you to everyone
who arranged today's ceremony,
even though I clearly told you
that I didn't want one."
"I hope going forward,
we will meet for business matters,
not for such impractical
and ceremonial events."
"I will properly introduce myself soon."
-Is that it?
-"Thank you."
-"President Kang Tae-moo." That'll be all.
-This is amazing.
God, these bastards! Damn it!
Oh, he's mad!
Look!
So where is the president?
The new president sure
seems like an interesting person.
Why won't it just go straight? Come on!
Come on, you're just stressed
because of the chairman's grandson.
Yes. Everyone thought you were
going to become the new president.
That kid snatched it away.
We still believe in you, Mr. Park!
I think this might help you feel better.
What's this? And what's with
that suspicious look on your face?
Ta-da!
I tucked the rest nicely
in the trunk of your car.
What is this?
It's beautiful!
It went in!
That was amazing!
But who the hell was that?
Where are your manners?
It's been a while, Mr. Park.
Look who it is? Tae-moo!
Or should I say, President Kang?
Why are you here?
What about the inauguration?
I heard you've been working hard.
Taking bribes from friends, relatives,
and even from your mistress
to sell contracts to be our partners.
Wait a second.
I think you've been hearing rumors.
You even hired a D-list celebrity
for the company ad
just because he's your nephew.
I saw it at the airport.
No, that's…
You must have thought it was okay
to take advantage of our company like that
since the chairman's turned
a blind eye to what you do.
President Kang, listen.
It's not like that.
I've been inattentive to company matters,
spending so much time abroad.
I intend to pay closer attention
from now on.
I'll see you tomorrow, then, Mr. Park.
Hey, President Kang!
Wait, President Kang!
President Kang.
Mr. Park! Are you okay?
-What is this?
-Damn it.
-What's going on?
-What is this?
Since it's Ms. Shin's birthday, I made
reservations at Auntie's Street Food
for our team dinner today.
Ms. Shin's favorite!
All right. How long has it been?
Oh, you guys didn't have to do that
just for my birthday.
Thank you.
What are you talking about?
A team's got to stick together.
You're buying, right?
Great!
Happy birthday. Can you swing by?
I have something for you.
Ms. Yeo, I'm sorry, but I don't think
I can make it to the team dinner today.
Why? What is it?
Is it a guy?
How did you know?
Because your soulless eyes
are suddenly sparkling. That's how.
Okay, go on.
It looks like we'll have to celebrate
Ms. Shin's birthday
without the birthday girl.
An inauguration without the president,
and a birthday party
without the birthday girl?
What's going on?
Seriously. This is like celebrating
Thanksgiving without a turkey.
I'm sorry.
I promise the next dinner is on me!
Hello?
Ha-ri!
I'm so busy, I can't even meet up
with you on your birthday.
So what's my girl got planned?
Min-woo wants to see me,
so I'm heading over.
One moment.
Min-woo?
Why is he calling you on your birthday?
After he made you
do all that work for his new menu?
That was hardly work.
I had a blast, and I learned a lot too.
Goodness, you're really head-over-heels
for Min-woo.
But he's never been the type
to remember birthdays. Why is he--
Wait, no way!
No way, what?
Was that necklace from before
really your birthday gift?
Necklace?
Why is a woman's necklace here?
Maybe some customer left it behind.
There's even a certificate
of authenticity!
Look, this is garnet!
That's my birthstone.
Is he dating a girl born in January?
Remember that foreign model girl?
She went back to her country
after Min-woo rejected her.
Then is it that journalist
writing an article on his restaurant?
She was flirting with Min-woo
but stopped after he friendzoned her.
The YouTuber then!
That YouTuber?
She asked him out on a livestream.
And got rejected live. Right.
Maybe it's your birthday present.
You think? Let me see.
No, this is way too expensive
to buy for a friend.
-Right?
-Yeah.
It has to be!
That necklace really was for you!
You said that it was too expensive
to buy for a friend.
Well, what if he's planning to transfer
from the friendship train
to the boyfriend express?
If you are transferring to Train 6,
please exit at the next stop.
The exit is to the right.
-Has the inauguration been taken care of?
-Yes, it went well.
What about the chairman?
You crazy bastard.
I told you to come to the inauguration.
You blow me off.
I told you to meet me at the house,
but you meet me at work.
You're determined to go against me,
aren't you?
Of course not. I've simply been too busy.
You just flew back in today!
You can't take a single damn day off?
No, I can't. There are too many things
that need to be taken care of.
What now?
Why the hell does Park keep on calling me?
What things need to be taken care of?
This is a well-oiled machine.
You're nitpicking.
You think you're
the only smart one in the world.
Are you realizing that now?
You know none of
my projects has failed, right?
Even the kimchi project
was a hit overseas.
Yes, I'm aware. That's actually why
I've prepared a very important
project for you.
What kind of project?
Marriage!
Are you getting married, sir?
Not me!
No, thank you.
I'm too young to get married.
But I'm not getting any younger, you know.
Is it too much to ask to see
my grandson with a wife?
Yes, it's too much. I'm not seeing anyone,
and I don't plan to anytime soon.
Besides, I have a lot of work to do.
That's why I've arranged
all the blind dates for you.
-What?
-I've put together a list
of 20 elite, single ladies
in the business world for you to meet.
All you have to do is show up.
Okay?
You made the list yourself?
Wow, that couldn't have been easy.
That's right, it wasn't easy.
If I had anyone else do it,
the entire finance sector
would be buzzing with rumors.
-So--
-You've wasted your time.
I won't ever go
on any of your arranged dates.
You little brat.
What am I going to do with you?
What is it?
ALARM 9:00 P.M.
TIME TO WATCH DRAMA
It's time already, huh?
It's already time.
BE STRONG, GEUM-HUI
It's started already.
NO-EUL
JU HUI-JAE
KIM JEONG-HWA
Let's see.
If you're just going to watch TV, go home.
Do you think I'm going to listen to you
when you don't listen to me?
I'll watch it here.
It's been quite a while
since he broke up with Yu-ra.
Maybe he's finally noticed that you've had
a crush on him and is ready to accept?
No way.
What? Why is it so dark?
Is Min-woo really--
Attention, please.
Min-woo is about to transfer
from the friendship train
to the boyfriend express.
What are you waiting for?
Run to him and give him a hug already!
Run!
Min-woo.
GYU-SIK LOVES BO-HUI
HAPPY 100TH DAY
What's her problem?
This is so annoying.
Yikes, I really messed that up for you,
didn't I?
It's okay.
I was doing it since they're regulars.
I just gave them the food for free.
Anyway, sorry. You must be busy.
I'll get going.
Wait a second.
Happy birthday, Ha-ri.
BUSINESS PROPOSAL
A DAY TO SKETCH
Happy birthday, Ha-ri.
Tickets to your favorite singer's concert.
They weren't easy to get, so make sure you
go with a guy and not with Young-seo.
Okay.
Go on.
You have no clue what I really like.
Good going.
You're eating instant food
as your first meal back in Korea
when you know how to cook everything
from Korean to Western!
Wouldn't it be nice
to sit at the dinner table with your wife
and enjoy a good home-cooked meal?
I'm not getting married just for that.
I hear American women are beautiful.
Did you really not date at all?
I'm open-minded, you know.
I have no time for that.
I'm busy enough with work.
That's why I've scheduled
your blind dates for you. So--
I told you I'm not interested, didn't I?
Are you two dating?
-What?
It seems that way.
You two are joined at the hip,
using work as an excuse.
I don't know about him, but I'm not gay.
And even if I liked men,
-President Kang isn't really my style.
-Is that so? Not your style?
Hey, what do you mean?
What's wrong with me?
Fine. If you're not, you're not.
Then why are you
so against going on these dates?
What is it now?
ALARM 10 P.M.
TIME TO TAKE BLOOD PRESSURE MEDS
Ah, shoot…
I can take care of myself,
so just go watch your TV shows.
Isn't that alarm for them?
It's for my blood pressure medication!
My blood pressure is so high nowadays
because of you.
I'm taking pills every day!
How is that my fault?
It runs in the family.
It'd be your fault
if I got high blood pressure.
You little--
I'm calling your name
But the sun sets quietly
Without a response
SHIN JOONG-HAE AND THE WILDFLOWERS
GUITAR CLUB MEETING
Thank you.
Hey, everyone, help yourselves.
Eat up, guys.
Okay.
-Cheers!
-Bottoms up!
Cheers!
-Sir, can I get some more of these chips?
-Go ahead.
-Mom!
-Gosh, what? You scared me!
I told you that you have to coat
the chicken properly to make it crispy.
I told you you have to be thorough.
But I am tossing it!
If we're not going to do things right,
we should just close up shop.
I guess that's why
the chicken Ha-ri makes tastes better.
You're the best!
Of course! She works at a major company,
after all. She's different.
Why are you so edgy today?
It can't feel great to have to work
on your birthday, of all days.
So what? I'm the one
who gave birth after 20 hours of labor!
Toss and toss and toss…
Will he be all right?
Yes. His blood pressure's higher
than usual, but it's not serious.
What do you mean, it's not serious?
Last time, you said that my lungs,
kidneys, and small intestine
weren't doing great.
What? I did?
Doctor!
Oh, yes, that's right. I remember now.
Considering his age,
things can change drastically day by day.
And you said I should avoid stress
more than anything, right?
Yes, sir.
-Everyone around him should be careful.
-Did you hear that?
It seems you're fine,
so drop the act and get out of bed.
You! Do you really want
to see me die because of you?
I'm going to--
Since you're already here,
why don't you get a full checkup?
I'm leaving.
SEOUL KANGSUNG HOSPITAL
What's the point of group reservations?
You give them a discount,
and they just fill up on the free snacks.
Why has she been so grumpy all day?
Hey, Ha-ri.
Don't you have a boyfriend who can throw
you a birthday party or something?
I didn't leave anything in front of
-your store!
-What's going on?
I told you I saw it! This is yours!
You've got a big mouth for a kid!
-Yes, I do!
-What?
-Hey.
-What? What is it?
Why is this in front of our store?
I put it there for a minute
because a customer parked
in front of our store!
I know you put it here
whenever you get the chance.
Did you see me do it?
It's obvious!
We find fish bones all the time!
We don't sell fish! We sell chicken.
-Take it.
-We don't sell fish either.
It says it right there.
"Fish, dried fish, mackerel, so on."
-Take it.
-Honey, come on.
We're all neighbors here. There's no need
to fight. Let's talk it out.
-I'm doing this so we don't have to fight.
-Come on, take it!
This is a new shirt!
I had it shipped from abroad!
-You toss it! Do what you want with it!
-Hey, don't shove it at him!
I didn't…
You were the one who started it!
Get in here.
Man, breaking the neighbor's store sign
and everything…
I feel so bad.
Everyone in the Shin family
has such a temper!
As if it wasn't enough that Ha-min
started fighting, why did you do that?
I got this temper from you, Mom.
Yes, why are you blaming it on the Shins?
What? Since when did you two
get along so well?
You guys just have to
talk back like that, don't you?
It's because I take after you, Mom!
It's my birthday!
Why are you hitting me?
You can't keep on using that as an excuse!
I made you seaweed soup in the morning!
Isn't that enough?
You forgot to cook her seaweed soup today.
Just stop it.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, HA-RI
FROM MIN-WOO
Happy birthday, Ha-ri.
Tickets to your favorite singer's concert.
They weren't easy to get, so make sure you
go with a guy and not with Young-seo.
Fine. I said, fine.
Did you have a good night's sleep?
-I have something to tell you.
-I just got a call from Mr. Park.
So you're aware of the situation?
I'm going to fire Mr. Park.
What? Says who?
He selected the subcontractors illegally.
But he still did a lot for the company
working under your predecessor.
He built a summer house
on our company land.
And he used our employees
for his personal affairs.
He'll do it all over again
if we let him be.
Park's father is Sang-gu,
my good old friend who contributed
greatly to our company's success.
He asked me to take care
of his son for him when he passed--
You can take care of him personally
after letting him go.
Come on.
Then,
do me a favor in return.
Go on the dates!
-Grandfather, that's--
-Stop making excuses and just do it.
I'm breaking the promise
I made to my dead friend.
It's the least you could do.
Fine, I'll go on the dates.
You mean it? Really?
Ms. Ahn, you heard it too, right?
-Yes, sir.
-You're my witness, okay?
All right.
Ha-ri, why did you have to go
and lose your temper?
Wait, the total is 800,000 won…
My tiny monthly pay minus
money for my savings, work loan,
and spending money…
I barely have anything left.
Where am I going to get 800,000 won?
-Did you hear?
-Oh, my God!
You don't know?
I'm the only one who's heard?
Don't freak out, okay?
Mr. Park got fired.
-What?
-Are you sure you heard right?
He's one of the chairman's men,
but he got fired?
Why did they fire him?
Apparently, he's been accepting bribes
from the subcontractors.
I heard President Kang is really strict.
So it's true.
I know, right?
You guys don't seem shocked, though.
Hi, Young-seo.
So you got ahead of yourself and ended up
completely ruining somebody's event.
Hey, you're partially responsible.
You put ideas into my head.
INCOMING CALL
BIOLOGICAL FATHER
"Biological father"?
Did you fight with your dad again?
When were we ever on good terms?
Why is he calling me at this hour?
How could he tell me
about a blind date on the day of?
MANNA SNACK BAR
But I thought blind dates
were off the table
after you faked that exorcism
on your last one.
You're still getting offers?
I suppose the rumors didn't spread
as much as I had thought.
Damn it!
Wait for me.
So, who is it this time?
Is it the Dongseong Group?
Daemin Group?
I don't know. I didn't even ask.
I'm so busy with work already.
Rather than getting wrinkles
from working overtime,
isn't going on a blind date
with a wealthy guy more productive?
No, I'm never doing an arranged marriage.
I'm only going to marry out of love
with someone I meet through fate.
You're so spoiled,
talking about fate and all that.
So I was thinking.
I'm going to need your help again.
Hey, I told you I'd stop doing that
once I got a job.
I'll pass.
This is the last time, I swear!
Can't you just pretend
to be possessed just one more time
so I can stop going on
these blind dates for good?
You must be nervous.
You haven't said a word.
-What's wrong, Young-seo?
-No.
-Young-seo, are you all right?
Let go!
Do you have any idea
who you're addressing?
How dare you approach the noble host
of the spirit of the great general,
you filthy mortal?
Spirit of the great general?
What's that?
What the hell are you doing?
-What's gotten into you?
-Stay still.
If you value your life, stay still.
What have you done to make such a vengeful
maiden spirit attach herself to you?
Am I the only one who can see the ghost--
I looked up the heir of Daepoong Group,
and he was a huge playboy.
So I tossed in the maiden spirit part.
He was so terrified.
That's what I'm talking about.
Can you help me out again? Please?
No, do it yourself.
Come on,
my acting will only get me so far.
Help me.
No. I'm uncomfortable
with so many people knowing my face.
I'll pay you.
What? Tonight at seven?
Yes, sir. At the coffee shop
at the Imperial Hotel.
With Jin Young-seo from the Marine Group.
I have a full schedule today.
Tell them I'm busy.
I don't want to hear you say anything
about being too busy.
Sung-hoon, move some things around
and make the time.
This is exactly why I pay you so much.
And that's why I went ahead
and cleared your schedule.
It was easier at the overseas branch.
I hope you find a suitable partner
among the top ten candidates.
Why is that?
Number 11 is in Japan
and 17 is in Switzerland.
Do you want to travel
that far for a blind date?
What?
Or just get married
like the chairman wants.
Then I won't have to bother
with making time in your schedule
and you won't
have to waste any more time--
I'm just frustrated, that's all.
I mean, I get where
the chairman is coming from.
No.
I think it's a good idea.
Marriage.
Hello.
We're going for a tough girl concept
for Marine Beauty's new product line.
Let's pick the clothes you'll wear
to the blind date here.
Okay.
Something lacey like this
will look super intimidating.
Or a leather belt like this
to make a bold statement.
That looks tough! Let's go with this.
-Maybe I should be showing more skin?
-Yeah. Let's try on something else.
-No.
This?
Hey, you're doing this on purpose!
-That one's really not it.
-I'm cold.
That's the point.
It makes you look like you're crazy.
-I will not…
-Marry you!
You're like a cute little fox.
Bravo! Perfect.
You're so pretty.
The play has started, and now it's time
to flex your acting chops, Ha-ri.
No, wait.
I'm Young-seo now.
Jin Young-seo.
Ms. Jin Young-seo?
Yes.
What? Why is he so good-looking?
He's hot.
You are Ms. Jin, right?
Yes.
Please have a seat.
I wish I could take my time
appreciating his looks.
But I need to end things quickly. Right.
Why don't I start by being rude?
I don't even know who you are.
Your name is?
My name is Kang Tae-moo.
What? Kang, what?
Kang Tae-moo.
"Kang Tae-moo"?
Oops.
Kang Tae-moo.
Kang Tae-moo?
The president of our company,
Ms. Jin?
-Ms. Jin!
-Yes?
Is something wrong?
No. Not at all.
I need to pop to the bathroom.
Excuse me, where's the bathroom?
Over there? Okay.
Young-seo, please pick up, please!
Please leave your message after the tone.
Young-seo, you crazy wench!
This is ridiculous.
Right!
Let's run! I can just run away.
I just need to stay calm
and do what needs to be done.
There's 800,000 won on the line!
You can do this, Ha--
I mean, Young-seo.
Please.
Sure.
Don't be so nervous.
This guy doesn't know I'm Ha-ri,
an employee at his company.
He thinks I'm Young-seo from Marine Group.
It's so hot.
It's a bit hot in here, isn't it?
No man likes a woman
who reveals too much skin.
Aren't you cold?
Cold? No, this is perfect.
My body runs a bit hot, you see.
You have goosebumps all over your arm.
Crap.
I just get goosebumps a lot, you know.
On to the next step.
Oh, sorry!
Baby, did I scare you?
You took a little bump? It's okay!
Did you get startled too? My babies!
A woman crazy about luxury goods.
How's that for a turn-off--
What are you doing?
Sorry, it was a text from work.
You were saying?
This won't do. On to my last resort.
-I'm so sad.
-What?
I'm sad. You being so uninterested in me
makes Samantha and Rachel really sad.
Samantha and Rachel?
Yes.
The one on the left is Samantha,
and the one on the right is Rachel.
I spent a whopping ten million won a piece
on these babies.
Hi!
I bet you've never met anyone
as crazy as this before.
I'm rambling, aren't I?
Oh, my.
No.
I prefer an honest person like you
over a hypocrite who lies.
-What?
Why is he so positive?
This won't work.
I need to bring out the big guns.
Really? You really like me?
Oh, my.
Then should we…
get a room?
A room?
Yes, so that we can really
get down to business.
How's that?
There's no way that you'll like a woman
who wants to get a room on the first date.
No way…
Let's go.
Okay.
What is this?
What'll happen
if I just follow him into that room?
Let's run! The money's not worth it!
Oh! I'm sorry.
Where do you think you're going?
What are you doing?
What? You have no idea who I am, do you?
Wait, let go of me first. Who are you?
I'm Min-sik's girlfriend.
Who is Min-sik…
What are you doing?
Let go of her. Let's talk it out.
I think this woman's crazy.
You were in a room here
with Min-sik just an hour ago,
and now you're getting a room
with another guy?
What a piece of trash.
What are you talking about?
I don't even know who Min-sik is.
So you're going to play dumb?
Isn't this you?
This…
Why, that--
She does look similar, but…
Okay, she and I look similar, but…
I'm sorry, but long hair is a common look.
And these clothes are new this season,
so many people wear them.
Anyway, that's not me.
So you're going to keep lying.
You little--
Why don't you go get
your boyfriend under control?
It takes two to cheat,
it's not something she did on her own.
Let's go.
Those bastards!
Mr. Cha, where are you?
I just came out of the lobby.
Okay.
What the hell? I've just become
some crazy, cheating bitch.
This is so embarrassing.
No. Maybe this is for the better.
It takes two to cheat?
How dare you accuse me of two-timing?
-Are you saying it's a misunderstanding?
-Yes. Two-timing?
I've never done that in my life.
Though I have seen three
or four guys at the same time.
-What?
-I really like men.
I know you like honesty,
but this is a bit much, right?
Hey!
Stop right there!
I'm going to leave
before anything worse happens to me.
Bye!
Hey, wait--
I'm sorry.
What…
Stop, you bitch!
Mr. Kang.
Let's just go.
Didn't you say you were
driving Ms. Jin home?
-She's over there, leaving.
-Pardon?
Stop right there, you bitch!
So she got caught
having an affair and ran?
Yes. She said she really likes men
and that she sees
three to four guys at a time.
She sounds like the worst.
What else? Samantha and Rachel?
-What does that mean?
-Don't ask.
-Sounds like it was a big waste of time.
-Maybe.
Yes.
We just said bye, and I'm heading home.
The date's over already?
Sounds like it didn't work out.
Fine, let me talk to Sung-hoon.
So we can schedule the next date.
There's no need for that.
What?
You're going to break your promise
and stop going on these dates?
No.
I'm going to marry Ms. Jin Young-seo,
the lady I met tonight.
You, what?
How on earth could the blind date
be the president of your company?
So? How did it go?
How do you think it went?
I just did my job!
Oh, come on!
I used all the personalities
that guys hate,
so I'm sure he won't contact you again.
Thank you for completing the mission
even in a situation like that.
You're a true friend.
To partners in crime?
Yes, of course.
I'm so proud of you.
You've worked hard,
so I'll get the next round of drinks too.
Thanks.
I'm the only one who can see him
Hey! Why do you keep
ending my songs early?
It's depressing!
You're just adding more stress,
not relieving it.
Ballads relieve stress better.
By expressing how it feels to love--
I'm not doing it.
One, two, three, go!
I want to tell you
Even though you can only hear me
After the sad times have passed
Close your eyes and feel my heart
And my eyes looking toward you
I love you, just like this feeling
This is the end of the wandering
That I have dreamed of
It keeps repeating in this world
Dad? Is he calling about the blind date?
Yes, Dad?
I got 100 points?
I got 100 points! Yes! 100 points!
I got 100 points!
Young-seo, I got a 100!
Ha-ri,
what did you do?
What do you mean? I sang my heart out!
Not that!
What did you do to make
President Kang want to marry me?
What? He wants to marry you?
Not me, you.
You're the one who went on the blind date.
Tell me what happened!
Ha-ri!
What?
Are you really going
to marry Ms. Jin Young-seo?
-Yes, how many times do you have to ask?
-I just find it hard to believe.
She two-timed--
To marry a woman who dates
as many men as she likes?
Why is her past any problem?
Because I feel like it will be a problem
even after getting married.
I mean, she seemed like quite the woman.
Of course she is.
She's from the Marine Group.
Like Grandfather said, she'll be
a good asset for me. Should I let her go?
Still, you should marry someone
that you love--
Love? What is love?
You miss them
even when they're right there with you,
and your heart flutters
when you think about them.
I don't want to cling to mere emotion.
And wasting time
on blind dates is even worse.
Besides, I like Ms. Jin.
She's very open and honest.
Come on, fold them right.
You keep messing it up.
That wasn't me.
Those are the ones Ha-min made.
Come on. I'm good at folding.
I gave up on soccer as a kid,
gave up becoming a celebrity
in middle school,
and gave up studying in high school too.
Good for you!
I heard you gave the guy money
for his store sign and hospital bills.
-Where did you get the money?
-I got a bonus from work.
Didn't you say things at work were weird
because of the new president?
But he handed out bonuses right away?
He seems pretty cool.
Did you see him? Didn't you say
he's the chairman's grandson?
-What does he look like?
-I don't know.
-Is he handsome?
-I don't know!
Why are you asking me? Don't ask!
Goodness.
Why are you throwing a fit?
Who else would I ask?
She put on a show to stop folding boxes.
Hey, Ha-ri, get your butt back here.
She must be tired. Let her rest.
I'll fold the boxes twice as fast.
-Make that three times.
-Okay!
Hello?
I'm hiding out in a hotel right now
because of you, my friend.
Why a hotel?
Ever since President Kang
said he wanted to marry me,
my old man's been trying to get
our families to meet up! So I ran!
What are you going to do?
You'd better clean up your mess.
How is this my fault?
If he wants to marry you
even after the crazy act I pulled,
I'm sure he's after your family.
You think so?
People who have it all are
always the ones who want more.
His family's much wealthier than mine.
I told you we should go
with the exorcism stuff.
I'll bet my right hand and empty wallet
that he still would've wanted to marry you
even if we went all out with an exorcism.
So what do I do now?
Should I run away from home?
Or shave my head and become a monk?
Just meet President Kang
and tell him honestly.
Tell him that the woman he wants
to marry isn't Jin Young-seo,
that you sent someone else
to ruin the blind date.
Damn it, my dad is going to be so mad.
But it'll stop all of this talk
about marriage.
Just look on the bright side.
It's like a blessing in disguise.
Wait, what if I run
into President Kang at work?
Dang.
I'm getting goosebumps.
Hey.
A regular employee will never
run into the president at work.
-Don't worry about it.
-You think so?
Oh, wait.
Wait for me!
Damn it! Mr. Gye always gives me hell
if I arrive later than he does.
-Get in, miss.
-Pardon?
There's a lot of space, so hop in.
Are you getting in or not?
Well, I…
"A regular employee will never
run into the president at work"?
Whatever.
Mr. Chairman, what brings you
to the office this early in the morning?
It's my company. Am I not allowed to come?
This brat made
a shocking declaration yesterday
but didn't explain it,
so I followed him here.
What is there to explain?
I told you everything yesterday.
So you're really going to marry her?
Sir, let's discuss that upstairs.
You there.
SENIOR RESEARCHER
SHIN HA-RI
Ms. Shin Ha-ri?
What? Why is he calling me?
No, wait, how does he even know my name?
Yes?
You dropped your employee ID.
I see. Why did I drop that?
Can you give it…
Oh, thank you.
Doors closing.
Shin Ha-ri?
Are you really going to marry Young-seo?
Shin Ha-ri.
Shin Ha-ri?
EMPLOYEE PERSONAL RECORDS
I was right.
What do you mean, you were right?
That employee back there.
She made the proposal
for Bucket List Fish.
Oh, really?
She's the one you singled out
for coming up with the idea, right?
I remembered her
because her name was unique.
I thought she was quite competent.
-Even aside from the Bucket List Fish--
-Stop talking about work!
What's the big idea?
What do you mean?
You always said blind dates
were a waste of time.
And now you want to get married
after one blind date?
I'm giving you that granddaughter-in-law
you want so badly.
Really?
Does Young-seo want to marry you as well?
What do you think?
About what?
With my face, body, impeccable manners,
and flawless personality,
why would she say no?
You're right! No one would say no
to my handsome grandson!
Look at you.
Who would say no to you?
That's my boy.
Was Young-seo really that good?
I'm not sure, sir.
I didn't get a good look at her.
He lost his parents at a young age
and I was
always too busy to really be there
for him as his grandfather.
How nice would it be
for him to start his own family
and love and care for them?
This goes for you, too.
Aren't you going to get a girlfriend?
Don't just work all the time
like my grandson.
Go find a good girl for yourself
and introduce her to me.
Okay?
You ran into the president?
And in the elevator, of all places?
Yeah! Do you have any idea
how scared I was?
So meet with Mr. Kang as soon as possible
and take care of this situation!
Okay, fine. Don't worry.
Okay.
Things are not looking good.
Are you okay?
I told you not to fool around!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Hey, kid.
Is it okay to run around
with something like this?
Not okay, right?
If you promise not to do it again,
I'll show you a magic trick.
Promise.
Look.
Ta-da!
-Guess what this is.
-Poop?
Poop?
How does this look like poop?
It's a flower.
Here's the bud,
and right here are the leaves.
Anyway, what I'm trying to say is,
you can't be running around
with things like this.
Somebody might get hurt,
or you might ruin somebody's outfit
that's worth a fortune, okay?
-Okay.
-Good.
Let me pay you for the dry cleaning.
Oh, it's fine. I scribbled more
than he did anyway. Here you go.
Bye.
Oh, right! My car keys and wallet.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
He's handsome as hell.
He's absolutely gorgeous.
I've found my love.
Oh, yes. I'm sorry.
It's no problem.
I want to ask for his number so badly!
Who is this?
Hello?
What? President Kang wants to meet you?
Yeah, he just called me.
That's great!
You can meet and tell him the truth!
My dear friend,
could you go instead of me?
You must be crazy.
I have an important meeting.
Still. How can I go instead? No way.
What if I get caught?
Why would you get caught?
Just go and say you don't like him.
That you won't marry him.
Just say no really clearly. Please?
Forget it.
Put off your meeting or take a rain check.
Take care of it yourself.
You remember this scar here?
When I tried to teach that flirty girl
following Min-woo around a lesson,
I slipped and hit my head on a rock.
Of course, I remember.
You bled so much from your head
that you were called the Bloody Head
of Hannam-dong for a while.
Why is it here, of all places?
It's so close to Min-woo's restaurant.
Where is this guy?
CALLING
JIN YOUNG-SEO
Do you have two phones?
Oh, that's--
KANG TAE-MOO'S NUMBER
How dare you just get my number like that?
We're going to get married,
so I should know all your phone numbers.
I'm not planning to marry you.
How can I marry
someone I've only met once?
Then why did you ask me
to get a room with you?
Wasn't it because you liked me?
That was--
And you showing up to the date
means you're willing to get married, no?
I was forced to go.
I hate arranged marriages,
especially for business reasons.
Anyway, please just forget
about all this marriage talk.
Don't be like that.
Let's just get married.
Look here, do you think marriage
is some kind of joke?
How could you ask
just anyone to marry you?
Who says I'm going to marry just anyone?
The person I want to marry…
is you.
No way. I'm not going to marry
someone I barely know.
-Then let's go on just ten dates.
-What?
I'll give you a chance to get to know me.
Once you do,
you'll learn I have a lot of strengths.
And I'm quite good…
at many things.
What do you mean, you're good--
What were you thinking about?
I just meant that I'm good to women.
I'm confident that you won't want
to see other men while seeing me.
Forget it.
I don't want to marry you or date you,
so I hope to never see you again.
Is he crazy or just dying to get married?
Anyway, I think I've said enough
for him to not contact me again.
-Are you done already?
-Let's just go.
Damn it, this is what I was worried about!
I can't run into him looking like this!
Subtitle translation by: Su-in Choi
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs