Sub by ®NETFLIX
It's Okay To Not Be Okay - tvN
Synced by ParkMinYoung℠
Then why are you here?
If not for money or sex,
what are you here for?
I was hoping
I could see you again.
That's why I'm here.
Your eyes.
I wanted to see them again.
My eyes?
Your eyes
remind me of someone I used to know.
Who is that person?
Someone who's messed up.
Help me. Help!
Shall I help him?
Or not?
Wait.
A woman
whose eyes
completely lacked warmth.
That woman...
Were you afraid of her?
No, the opposite.
I liked her.
CHAPTER 2 THE LADY IN RED SHOES
OK PSYCHIATRIC HOSPITAL
Are you making a move on me now?
I remind you of the girl
in your beautiful memories?
I never said they were beautiful memories.
Do you still like me?
Don't jump to conclusions.
I wouldn't call them good memories.
Is that so?
But you know what?
Bad memories
stay here longer.
Hey, I can't believe
you let them run into each other!
You should've stopped Mun-yeong
at all costs.
Well, Ms. Ko showed up unannounced.
Does she ever give us a heads-up?
Gosh, seriously.
If you lack foresight,
you should've done all you could
to stop them.
Unbelievable! Why do I even pay you?
I want to punch him, even just once.
Go tell Mr. Lee that I understand
how tough his job must be.
What?
But he doesn't need
to go to such lengths for me,
so tell him not to contact me again.
My gosh.
I'm very late, aren't I?
The traffic was awful.
Why don't we have a chat
over some sweet beverage?
No, it's okay.
Oh, you're leaving already?
Don't forget to get Ms. Ko's autograph.
My autograph?
-Well, that's--
-Earlier, you asked me
to get Ms. Ko's autograph for you.
The spiel about my eyes
and that girl in your memories
was all just for my autograph?
No.
So you weren't after money or sex.
My autograph was what you wanted.
I said, no.
My gosh, this is perfect.
We can call this
an impromptu fan meet-and-greet.
-Why don't we drink this together--
-I'll give you one.
My autograph.
This is my newest book, hot off the press.
All right.
Name?
Moon...
Sang-tae.
Who is Sang-tae? Is he your nephew?
No, he's my brother.
I see. Your brother is a fan of hers.
Right, Mun-yeong has fans of all ages
and nationalities.
She has a huge fanbase.
Congratulations.
-Consider these fan goods--
-Here.
ZOMBIE KID
I'll be off, then.
See you again.
I don't think so.
Gosh, I have to make sure he takes this.
Mr. Moon!
Mr. Moon.
Mr. Moon, please. Hold on a second.
Goodness, just a second--
Gosh, my apologies.
I'm truly sorry about what happened,
so please take this.
50,000 WON
This is too much just for myself.
Well, then you can share it
with the people around you.
-Oh, I see.
-Yes.
Shall I do that, then?
Gosh, hey! No!
Hey, don't... Hey!
Hey, jeez.
I don't need this,
so don't follow me.
But... Wait.
I've been cleaning up after Mun-yeong
for the past ten years,
and no one has ever said no to this.
What an oddball.
Gosh, I'm getting
a bad feeling about this.
Should I have offered him
two boxes instead of one?
Beautiful.
I want him.
Did you ask for me?
The other day, you said
you want to be given a proper task.
Yes, just tell me what you need.
I'll do anything.
Do some digging on the man who just left.
-Pardon?
-If you tell Mr. Lee,
I'll pull out your tongue,
so you'd better keep this a secret.
ZOMBIE KID
KO MUN-YEONG'S NEWEST BOOK, COMING SOON
JAE-SU
Yes, we're eating now.
Hey, your landlady stopped by
early in the morning and lashed out at me.
Gross. It has your saliva on it.
It's gross. Your saliva.
Cover your mouth when you cough.
It's better than catching a virus.
Yes, he's doing great.
I mean, so far.
Hey, where did you have to go so early?
Are you working as a driver or something?
What? Ko Mun-yeong?
What? Her autograph?
Okay, talk to you later.
He got it.
Gosh, hold on. Wait!
Wait up. Can't we finish the food
before we go?
Hey! Wait!
Dear Sang-tae. I hope you can come
to my book launch party.
You can get my autograph
and take pictures with me.
We'll have fun.
Mun-yeong will be waiting for you.
Wink!
Jeez, what's wrong with her?
RETAIL SPACE FOR LEASE
What? Where do you need me to go?
Well...
I have to finish packing,
go persuade my landlady, and--
I want an outfit
that will make me look smart
like an Oxford University student.
I also have to tie up loose ends
at all my part-time jobs.
You sound like a spider pulling webs
from its butt. Stop rambling on.
So you're saying
you want me to take Sang-tae
to that woman's signing event, right?
Yes.
All right. Text me the time and location.
Thanks, Jae-su.
Who's your favorite? Me or Sang-tae?
You're so shy. You're such a cutie pie!
Hello!
Ju-ri.
Another fried chicken place?
Are you that excited?
"Dear Sang-tae!
I hope you can come
to my book launch party.
Autograph...
You can get my autograph
and take pictures with me.
We'll have fun.
Mun-yeong will be waiting for you. Wink!"
"Dear Sang-tae!" Yes!
Okay, Oxford University student.
My gosh, this is nice.
Sang-tae, try this one.
Yes, this one's cool.
Looking cool...
What do I do with my face to look cool?
Cool facial expressions.
How do I look cool?
-The beer is on the house.
-Well...
I have to go back this evening,
so I shouldn't drink.
-How about Coke?
-Sure, I'll drink Coke.
This is also on the house.
I heard you transferred
to a hospital in the countryside.
Right.
RETAIL SPACE FOR LEASE
By the way, are you moving again?
Well, you know.
I refuse to be tied down to one place.
I'm like the last nomad in this country.
Well... All is good, right?
Yes, as you can see.
No, I mean...
Gang-tae.
Yes. He's doing well,
getting joy out of overworking himself.
Did you hurt your hand?
-No, I'm okay.
-Take it easy.
Your wage won't go up
even if you work that hard.
They say one must seek out hard work
while still young, but that's bullshit.
Gosh, you'll see when you're older.
You'll suffer from body aches all over
and get sick all the time.
That young man is so unyielding.
All right, let's start the meeting.
-Okay.
-Yes, sir.
I'll start with the reviews.
Most reviewers said
that the illustrations are too grotesque.
Ms. Ko's other books were also criticized
for being too cruel.
I think the illustrations are adding
to that this time, so I'm worried.
Right. Then we should--
Just leave it the way it is.
Yes, we'll just leave it the way it is.
All right, what's next?
About Ms. Ko's book that will be adapted
into an animated film in the US...
You mean, The Ugly Dog's Puppy?
Right.
They called and said
that they want to change the dog character
to a cat.
Tell them to keep it as is. If they
change it, I will annul the contract.
Mun-yeong, then we'll suffer big losses...
Then would you rather suffer death?
Hey, Seung-jae! How could you think
it's okay to turn a dog into a cat
without the author's permission?
They're different species.
Tell them to stick
to the original characters and plot.
Hey, are you leaving?
Make sure the book signing event tomorrow
lasts no more than an hour.
As with anything else,
the faster we get it done, the better.
YOO SEUNG-JAE
Okay, Seung-jae?
Hello?
Uncle, I need you to do
a background check on someone.
I know you shouldn't do stuff like that
when you have sworn to protect and serve.
Then do you know anyone who works
at the National Intelligence Service
or at a private detective agency?
Hello?
Gosh, what do I do?
Thanks for your hard work.
You're so capable and efficient.
I'm sad that you're leaving.
Gang-tae.
Someone's looking for you.
What happened to your hand?
I hurt it a little while working.
I'm all sweaty.
Jae-su told me
that I'd be able to find you here.
I see.
I heard you're moving again.
You can leave whenever you want
without being attached to places.
I envy you for that.
Have you decided
which hospital to work at?
I'm sure I'll find a job somewhere.
I'm not sure if it's a good thing or not,
but they keep building
new psychiatric hospitals.
The hospital I work at is looking
for an experienced caregiver.
It's called OK Psychiatric Hospital.
Eight-hour rotating shifts.
You'll get ten days off each month,
so you can pick up a part-time job
on the side if you'd like.
And you're a certified nursing assistant,
so you'll get extra pay.
Where is the hospital?
In Seongjin City, our hometown.
You said you also lived there
when you were little.
A bunch of areas have been redeveloped,
so it no longer has that small-town vibe.
Also, a multiplex theater
opened recently and...
Mom.
Mom!
Bring my mom back.
Mom.
Mom, no.
-Mom, open your eyes.
-The butterfly did it.
I mean, I saw it.
-Mom!
-The butterfly...
Mom, no.
-Mom, please open your eyes.
-The butterfly
killed Mom.
The butterfly...
The butterfly killed her.
I saw it.
The butterfly did it.
Sang-tae! Tell us exactly what you saw.
Was it a man or a woman?
How old?
What did this person look like?
Did you hear the voice?
The butterfly said it'd kill me as well
if I didn't keep my lips sealed.
It said it'd chase me down
and kill me!
We should send the younger one
to a children's home
and his older brother to a center that
takes care of children with special needs.
That would probably be best for them both.
Okay. We'll leave him in your hands, then.
Sang-tae, let's go.
Come on.
Where are we headed?
To a place where the butterfly
can't find us.
Somewhere far?
Yes, far away.
You must be tired.
You didn't have to come with me.
Get on the bus. You'll arrive very late.
Bye, then.
Hey, Gang-tae.
There's an empty room at my place.
I mean...
No one uses the room.
My mom and I only use the first floor.
If you actually end up
moving back to Seongjin City,
you won't have to look for a place.
Bye now, for real.
Thanks for your concern,
but I won't be moving there.
Why not?
Because it's in the countryside?
Yes.
That's why.
Ju-ri, I don't know if you know this.
Gang-tae, that poor thing,
never builds deep relationships.
He'll leave eventually anyway,
so he thinks it's pointless to build
a relationship that will only last a year.
-Why does he keep...
-Right,
but why does he have to leave?
It's because...
What's the reason?
You see, it's all...
It's all because of that damn butterfly.
Darn it.
"Butterfly"?
A butterfly?
See you again.
I don't think so.
ORTHOPEDICS
VIBRANT ORTHOPEDICS PHYSICAL THERAPIST
JINCHEON, NORTH CHUNGCHEONG PROVINCE
OK PSYCHIATRIC HOSPITAL
DIRECTOR O JI-WANG
IS KOREA'S NUMBER ONE PTSD EXPERT
ACCORDING TO DIRECTOR O, "ONE MUST
FACE ONE'S TRAUMA TO OVERCOME IT"
-"What do you want for Christmas?
-What do you want for Christmas?
-A teddy bear? Cookies? Candy canes?
-A doll?"
-A doll?
-"No need to use separate products!
-No need to use separate products!
-With this one product,
-you can maintain healthy scalp and hair.
-Say goodbye to hair loss."
-Say goodbye to hair loss.
No more hair loss!
"A true gentleman's scent."
Be the cool guy.
"Be the cool guy."
I like Ms. Ko Mun-yeong! I like her!
Jae-su, please...
Don't worry, Gang-tae. You have me.
GANG-TAE
"Disinfect and eliminate odors
in one blow!"
In one blow! Done!
Right, Jae-su. When will he be here?
Gosh, Jae-su...
Jae-su.
ZOMBIE KID
KO MUN-YEONG BOOK SIGNING EVENT
BOOK SIGNING EVENT THIS WAY
My gosh, he's so tall.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
Oh, no! It's cold!
Sang-tae! Don't run!
Look left and right. Be safe.
Safety comes first.
Look at those blue pants. Blue jeans.
I'm so happy now.
My name is Lee Un-jae.
Thank you.
-Oh, is this it?
-My gosh!
-Jeez!
-Gosh! What are you doing?
-I'm sorry.
-All right.
-Wait, Sang-tae.
-Yes.
Sang-tae, hey. Sang-tae!
-Listen up.
-Okay.
-You see the restroom over there, right?
-Yes.
-You see it?
Good. When you're getting
her autograph later,
I'll be watching you
from exactly that distance,
-so get that woman's autograph--
-Author Ko Mun-yeong?
That's right.
After you get Ko Mun-yeong's autograph
and take a picture with her,
we'll head home right away.
Then what will you get?
Buy me the dinosaur encyclopedia.
Sang-tae, don't run. Sang-tae!
-Let's go.
-Slow down.
-Wait, Sang-tae.
-What?
You must wait in line.
-Wait here, okay?
-Okay.
-I'll be over there.
Okay, let's go.
I'm getting her autograph.
THE QUEEN OF CRIME FICTION
DO HUI-JAE'S POSTHUMOUS WORK
THE MURDER OF THE WITCH OF THE WEST
WRITTEN BY DO HUI-JAE
The mother
is the Queen of detective fiction.
And her daughter
is the Queen of children's literature.
They're quite something, aren't they?
My goodness, what brings
a busy man like you all the way here?
Of course I should be here
to congratulate you on the new release.
As you know, I exclusively review
and critique Ko Mun-yeong's books.
Right, that's true.
Seven of her books are in the top ten list
of the best-selling children's books.
BOOKS OF THE MONTH
I have to say, it's really impressive.
Do you think
it's because of Ko Mun-yeong's looks?
Gosh, come on.
It's not because of her looks.
It's because she's a great writer.
All right, let's not stand around here.
Why don't we go somewhere
and drink something sweet?
-Let's go.
-Goodness, what's with you?
Come on. It's okay.
Why are you being like this? I'm diabetic.
Come on. You'll be fine. Excuse us.
The sun is...
What time is it? What?
What time is it? I'm late!
What the fuck, 18 calls?
I'm so dead.
Shit, what do I do?
Jeez.
-Sang-tae, I have to take a call.
-Okay.
-Stay right here, okay?
Gosh!
My, it's a stegosaurus.
A real stegosaurus. Hi, stegosaurus.
-A stegosaurus.
-My gosh.
This is a stegosaurus.
The name means "roofed lizard."
It's okay. You don't need to come.
The plates.
Stegosaurus is characterized
by the plates along the back.
It's estimated that they lived
during the late Jurassic Period.
-The scientists--
-What's wrong with him?
What's with you?
My gosh, this stegosaurus is huge!
It has a small brain
despite its large size--
Get lost!
-My gosh.
-Oh, no!
I have a plush toy
that looks just like it.
Here, this looks just like it.
This is my stegosaurus toy.
Its name is Teary--
-I'm being too nice, aren't I?
-My hair.
-Get out.
-My hair. Let go!
-I said, get out!
-My hair...
-Get out.
-No, my hair!
Don't touch my hair!
My hair... Don't touch my hair.
Don't touch my hair.
My hair! Don't touch my hair!
Don't touch my hair. Go away.
Don't touch my hair. Go away!
Sorry, excuse me.
-Go away!
-Sang-tae, it's okay.
-No, my hair...
-Sang-tae, I'm sorry.
-He grabbed my hair...
-I'm sorry, Sang-tae.
-You're okay now.
-I'm okay.
-It's okay. I'm sorry.
-You're okay now, Sang-tae.
-I'm okay now. I'm sorry.
I'm okay now.
I'm okay now. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Shall I help him?
Or not?
Hey!
You need to apologize.
You.
Apologize.
-Why should I apologize to him?
-No, to me.
What?
You totally ruined my book signing event.
Why is that my fault?
This fucking dumbass--
Goodness!
Gosh!
Who wouldn't scream when someone
grabs them by the hair like this?
See? You're screaming too.
Let go. I said, let go!
-Let go.
-Listen.
This lunatic was harassing our son.
-What did you expect? Just watch?
-Shit. I'm so screwed.
Are you a psychiatrist?
How do you know that he's a lunatic?
Well, that's...
I can tell because he kept
rambling on about things
that make no sense!
Crazy bitch.
-My gosh.
-Did she really just say that?
-What's with her?
-Goodness.
What did you just say?
Well, you kept rambling on
about things that make no sense,
so I thought you were crazy.
My gosh. Honey, you heard that, right?
You all heard that, right?
She swore at me just now.
What are you people doing? Record this!
Yes! Record a video!
-I'm speechless.
-Film this!
I'm utterly speechless.
I'm okay. I'm not a bad person.
I'm not a bad person.
INVENTORY
Shouldn't you check on him?
He'll let me in when he's calmed down.
When would that be?
Usually in an hour.
A day or two at the most.
Then what? I have to stay here all night?
No, I never asked you to.
Don't worry.
Just go sort out the situation.
"Don't worry"?
Why would I worry? About whom?
By the way, the back of his head
must be very sensitive.
Is that his erogenous zone or something?
Oh, it's like a detonator.
When it's set off, the bomb goes off.
Then how does he get haircuts?
Will he go like this again? "No!"
Enough, okay?
Now, you're looking at me in the eye.
What are you doing?
Don't wear hats.
I can't see your pretty face.
Why is your face turning red?
Your forehead must be
your erogenous zone, right?
Hey, Ms. Ko!
You caused trouble again.
Mr. Lee will be really stressed out
this time.
Gosh, seriously!
Why does she get herself in trouble
whenever I'm not around?
She acts up
whenever that caregiver shows up.
Hey, if you knew that,
why didn't you make sure
they wouldn't run into each other?
Gosh, why do I even pay you?
Hi, Reporter Kim.
Gosh, no. She never said, "Crazy bitch."
She just said,
"Gosh, this is driving me crazy."
People mishear things all the time,
you know.
That fucking prick.
Is he your boyfriend?
My gosh, you're dating?
If you got those boxes,
just shut up and leave.
Gosh, you look exactly like your mother
now that you have a frown on your face.
Your mother was not only a great writer,
but she was also very sexy.
You have a lot in common with your mother.
Cut the nonsense and just leave.
Things might be great now,
but I advise you to be careful.
Her mother, who was a famous writer,
suddenly passed away
without a single warning.
And her father, who was
a successful architect, suddenly went nuts
and got locked up
in a psychiatric hospital.
Then what do you think will happen to you?
You won't end up well
if you get involved with her.
Keep that in mind.
Let me go.
Don't go.
Do you like me?
Are you going to look after me?
Do you think you can handle it?
Who are you to stop me?
I was right.
I knew you'd come after me.
I've been reading your books
for quite a long time now.
And when you read someone's book,
you can easily see
how that writer thinks and feels.
Then I guess you also know
what I'm going to do next.
Don't mess with me.
I won't go down alone.
I'll take you and Mr. Lee down with me.
Why do you think they call me
the Suicide Bomber?
Isn't it because you're a jerk
who never goes down
without taking others with you?
Isn't that right?
I can destroy your career
with the tip of my pen.
I'm sure you know that.
A famous children's book writer
actually turned out to have
an antisocial personality disorder?
What do you think will happen
when people find out?
What do you want?
I'm starting to get tired and bored
of receiving these boxes.
I think it'd be nice
if you'd be kind enough
to humor me a little.
That's easy.
But I, too,
can attack you with the tip of my pen.
Goodbye.
911 EMERGENCY
You evil bitch!
You just wait! I swear I'll get rid of...
Loosen your neck, sir.
Damn, he should've just died.
Why do all jerks have a long lifespan?
Damn it.
Stop right there.
What are you doing?
Take in a deep breath.
Deeper.
-What are you--
-Close your eyes.
When you can't control yourself,
cross your arms like this
and take turns
tapping on each shoulder like this.
This will help you calm down.
What is this?
The Butterfly Hug Method.
It's a self-healing technique
that's recommended for trauma patients.
It's no fun to have you stand behind me.
A trauma
should be faced head-on like this
instead of trying to soothe it
from behind.
Why are you running away?
I'm going to my brother.
Slow down. My feet hurt.
Hey.
Hey!
Don't make me get angry. I'll explode.
That's why I taught you
the butterfly hug method.
That stuff is useless.
-I want you to be my safety pin.
-What?
Keep me under control
so that I won't explode.
You told me to mind my own business.
You told me I had no right to stop you.
You hold grudges.
Yes, that's right.
So I'm giving you the right to be
Ko Mun-yeong's safety pin.
Why would I be your safety pin?
Because you're a caregiver.
Isn't it your job to keep an eye
on potential patients and care for them?
Go and ask someone else.
I'll pay you a lot of money.
How much do you want?
There's something we always say
to patients who fully recover.
What's that?
"Hope I never see you again."
Please.
Let's not meet again.
I really want you to stop.
Stop following me.
But I'm not a patient.
"Hope I never see you again."
That's what you say to your patients.
But I'm fine.
You're right.
You're different from patients.
Exactly.
Drugs and injections can't cure you.
You were just born that way.
So there's no way to treat you.
And you have a poor prognosis.
It's just best
to avoid people like you.
You're not avoiding me.
You're just running away
because you're scared.
You coward.
Hey.
Do you
still like me?
Coward.
Mun-yeong.
How are you going to deal with this?
There were tons of witnesses!
Why are you always ruining your own career
that you worked for?
What were you doing?
You were smoking, weren't you?
-Yes.
-My gosh, come on.
Mun-yeong!
Why don't you just kill me?
Sang-tae.
Are you upset
that you didn't get her autograph?
If you keep looking so upset,
you're going to make my heart ache.
-Gosh, my stomach.
-Why does your stomach hurt?
-My stomach...
-Your stomach... 911...
-Call 911.
Surprise!
The Dinosaur Encyclopedia.
The Dinosaur Encyclopedia!
It's The Dinosaur Encyclopedia!
The Dinosaur Encyclopedia.
Are you happy?
Yes, I'm happy. I'm really happy.
Who do you like more? Me or Ko Mun-yeong?
"Maiasaura's name means
'good mother reptile' in Latin.
It's a herbivorous dinosaur
with a duck-like beak.
Dromaeosaurus' name means
'swift running lizard',
and it got its name due to its fast speed.
It's about 35cm big when it hatches
from the mother's egg,
and it grows up to 3m in just a year.
Maiasaura. Maiasaura.
Maiasauras lived in herds
and took care of their infants
until they grew up to about one meter.
Maisaura means 'good mother reptile'.
Bagacera... Bagaceratops.
It means 'small-horned face'.
Bagaceratops."
What are you doing?
Don't wear hats.
I can't see your pretty face.
It's a reptile.
"Bagaceratops is a dinosaur with horns.
It has a small body and short tail.
Bagaceratops lived in the desert
and dug holes in the sand
to lay eggs there.
A dinosaur with small horns.
A dinosaur with ghastly claws,
Baryo... Baryonyx."
EMERGENCY AMBULANCE
Check his vitals and blood pressure
on your way there.
What about the epinephrine?
I have some ready just in case.
Do you have the list of medications
and medical history card?
Here.
Thanks. I'll be off now.
Let's get going.
Good luck.
"It is very nimble and fast.
Dromaeosaurus' name means
-'swift running lizard..."
-Sang-tae.
Sang-tae!
"Its body and tail..."
I told you not to get distracted
when you're walking.
Don't you remember you got hit by a car
and got hospitalized?
-Give it to me.
-No!
Give me that.
You can read it at home.
-Come on.
-No.
-It's dangerous.
-Look!
-Sang-tae! No, don't run.
-I'll be safe. Let's be safe.
-Don't run. It's dangerous.
-Slowly. Let's take my time.
-Look.
-You can't fool me again. Give it to me.
Jae-su... It's Jae-su.
You know me, right?
Even a ton of beer
can't make me get drunk.
But it's weird how I get so easily drunk
whenever I drink with a woman.
A long time ago, a wise man once said,
"History is made at night
with alcohol and a woman."
But my history
is going to be pitch dark.
Utterly dark.
Jae-su.
Yes?
It's time that you stop.
Stop what?
Living a hard life by following us around.
You should settle down
and live comfortably.
What's your problem? That's up to me.
Who are you to decide what I should do?
I'll decide when it's time for me
to stop or not.
What's the matter with you?
Did something happen?
Why are you so sentimental today?
That darn woman, Ko Mun-yeong.
That crazy woman did something again,
didn't she?
-No.
-Don't lie to me.
-No, she didn't.
-She obviously did.
You never mean it when you say "no."
What did she do?
I thought I was on the run
because of my brother.
The butterflies and all.
I thought we were being chased
by something that doesn't even exist
all because of Sang-tae.
Well, it's true.
But today, for the first time,
I suddenly thought
maybe I was just running away
because I wanted to.
That's not true.
You see,
when life is unbearably hard,
the easiest way out is to run.
THE BOY WHO FED ON NIGHTMARES
This is Ms. Ko Mun-yeong's book.
Ko Mun-yeong.
Sang-tae, do you remember
where we used to live when we were young?
Where we used to live with Mom.
Seongjin City.
Right.
Should we
go live there?
If you don't want to--
Sure.
Are you really okay?
The Chinese restaurant there
sells really good jjamppong.
It's right at the entrance of the market.
It has mussels and chili pepper inside.
The broth tastes amazing.
Sang-tae.
It's the best.
You're really brave.
I'm a coward.
You're the younger brother.
That's why you're a coward.
You're a coward
because you're the younger brother.
Trust me.
I'm the older brother,
you can count on me.
Trust me. You can trust me.
-That's such a relief.
-Yes.
Who is that?
Is he your boyfriend in Seoul?
What?
Go ahead and pick up.
MOON GANG-TAE
Hello?
Hey.
Yes.
DOB: JULY 14, 1991
BORN IN OJI-GUN, SEONGJIN CITY
"Seongjin City"?
No wonder.
Your eyes remind me of
someone I used to know.
SANGSANGESANG PUBLISHERS
We know nothing about it.
It was a misunderstanding. All rumors.
We can't reach Ms. Ko either.
Yes. Just a second.
-Hello?
-This fucking dumbass--
KO MUN-YEONG ABUSES AND SWEARS AT A FAN
AT HER BOOK SIGNING EVENT
My goodness.
-Let go of me.
-Listen.
This lunatic was harassing our son.
What did you expect?
Just watch?
Crazy bitch.
...so I thought you were crazy.
Didn't you...
collect all the CCTV footage
from the bookstore?
This video was uploaded this morning
on an online mothers' forum.
-Ko Mun-yeong abused and swore at a fan
-My goodness.
at her own book signing event
and made her fans get extremely shocked
and disappointed at her.
She suddenly asked me to apologize
and started yanking my hair.
I'm already suffering hair loss.
"Crazy bitch."
She called me that and started laughing.
It totally gave me the creeps.
Ever since then,
I've been getting nightmares.
Everyone, stay focused.
I think we should visit them
and compensate them for what happened.
That is not all.
After the recent incident,
Ko Mun-yeong's bizarre past
went viral online.
KO MUN-YEONG’S BIZARRE PAST ACTIONS
GET EXPOSED AND SHOCK HER FANS
Read it out loud.
Don't you know what that is?
-Oh, right.
What do you brats think a fairy tale is?
The brat on the very back. You tell me.
-What did she just say?
-Did I just hear her wrong?
-Don't you know?
-It's okay, everyone.
It's how she calls all kids.
Not a big deal.
-Kids are cute. Cute brats.
-What?
What's the big issue?
-It's used in an affectionate way.
-Are you kidding me?
Lovable brats, right?
-What's the big issue?
-People are raising an issue about
the famous fairy tale writer
who has been instilling dreams and hopes
to many kids around the world.
Meanwhile, some even say
her name should be removed
from the list of candidates
for the Hans Christian Andersen Award.
I... Well...
Sir, what should we do?
I don't think money can solve this one.
No... No, that's not true.
It's okay, you guys.
We've been through worse.
There has to be a way out.
Sir!
We're in trouble.
Why? What is it this time?
A civic group applied for an injunction
against selling Ms. Ko's new book,
Zombie Kid,
saying the storyline and illustration
of the book are too grotesque.
Where is Mun-yeong right now?
Where is Ko Mun-yeong?
WELCOME TO OJI-GUN, SEONGJIN CITY
Where is Mun-yeong?
She checked out of her hotel room.
Oh, okay. Then I should
also check out from my life.
-Mom!
-Sir!
-No!
-Catch him!
Mom!
Sir! Stop him!
Sir! No, sir!
Sir, stop!
Mr. Lee!
I think
it's all because of me.
What?
To be honest,
I sent this to Ms. Ko this morning.
INFORMATION ON MOON GANG-TAE
"Moon Gang-tae"?
The caregiver?
OK PSYCHIATRIC HOSPITAL
There we go.
MR. LEE
ANSWER
Mun-yeong, where are you?
Tell me where you are!
Do you know The Red Shoes
written by Hans Christian Andersen?
What are you talking about
all of a sudden?
Where are you right now?
OK PSYCHIATRIC HOSPITAL
It's raining.
-Gosh, it's raining.
-Everyone, let's go inside.
-It's raining.
-Let's go inside.
Don't run.
-Be careful, everyone.
-Let's go inside.
OK PSYCHIATRIC HOSPITAL
The little girl wore her red shoes
everywhere she went,
even to a God-fearing church.
Once you wear those shoes,
your feet start dancing on their own.
And you can never stop dancing
or take off those shoes.
But even so,
the little girl
never gave up on those red shoes.
In the end, the executioner
had to cut off her feet.
But the two feet that got cut off
still continued to dance
in those red shoes.
Some things can't be torn apart
no matter how hard you try to do so.
Don't tell me...
Yes, the ones in the rooms are fine.
But the lights in the lobby
and the reception area are out.
Yes, okay.
That is why
obsession is noble and beautiful.
I have
finally found my red shoes.
Why
are you here?
Why do you think?
I came because I missed you.
Sub by ®NETFLIX
It's Okay To Not Be Okay - tvN
Synced by ParkMinYoung℠
How can you define a relationship
in just one word?
Please teach a class, Ms. Ko.
I'm Ko Mun-yeong. I'll be teaching
this writing class from now on.
I have no time to play with you.
Hypocrite.
I know you want some fun.
I am growing forgetful these days.
Even Sang-tae.
You're not running away.
You're making
me worried.
Subtitle translation by Ja-won Lee