Sub by ®NETFLIX
It's Okay To Not Be Okay - tvN
Synced by ParkMinYoung℠
A long time ago,
there lived a beautiful girl in a castle
located deep inside the forest.
She was always alone,
so she was lonely and bored.
So one day, she left the castle
to find herself a friend to play with.
She offered them
all sorts of amazing gifts,
but nobody ever accepted her.
Later on, she found out why.
A monster who brings along
the shadow of death.
That's what the people called her.
"She's a monster. A monster."
She was very angry
at every living soul in the world.
And she needed to take it out on someone.
Ever since she had unexpectedly
saved the boy from dying,
the scary shadow that always
followed her around suddenly disappeared.
And the boy always
followed her around instead.
He always went with her
whether it was day or night
and whether she was in the mountains
or on a field.
On a clear and sunny day,
the girl asked him this.
"Hey, will you always stay by my side?"
"Of course. I will never run away."
"Even after you see this?"
The girl was all alone again,
and that's when the shadow of death
came back and whispered this.
"No one can ever stay by your side
because you're a monster.
Do not ever forget that.
Do you understand?"
Yes, Mother.
CHAPTER 1 THE BOY WHO FED ON NIGHTMARES
THE BOY WHO FED ON NIGHTMARES
This stop is Daun Vocational School.
The next stop is...
I mean, he threw a huge fit
in the middle of class.
My goodness.
No!
There's no use in trying to stop him.
And this isn't the first time.
Your expression shows your emotions
What if there was a dangerous tool
right next to him?
It would've led to an accident.
I don't understand
why we always need to walk on eggshells
-because of Sang-tae.
-Is he angry?
Is he angry?
-Anyway, we need to think of safety,
-Angry...
-Getting annoyed.
-and he's too much for us to handle.
Just send him to a special needs school
or a local community center.
That will be best for everyone.
-Your expression shows your emotions
-Tell me what you think.
What do you think?
Will you please say something?
My gosh, seriously.
He's angry.
THE BOY WHO FED ON NIGHTMARES
MOON SANG-TAE
Sang-tae.
Aren't you hungry?
What do you want to eat?
You weren't planning to stay here
for that long anyway.
I'll find you a better school
once we move.
I promise.
-Are you that upset?
-Jjamppong.
-What?
-Tangsuyuk with sauce on the side.
Let's not go to Jageumseong.
Let's eat at Yangjagang.
Okay, let's stuff ourselves with food
at Yangjagang.
The food is really good there.
Do you remember?
When was the last time we went?
Don't worry. I'll buy.
I'm your big brother.
By any chance, are you
Author Ko Mun-yeong?
-Yes.
-See? I told you.
My daughter is a big fan of yours.
I'm sorry to ask this,
but can we please get your autograph?
-Your name?
-Lee Seul-bi.
She's really beautiful in real life,
isn't she?
Yes, she's like a princess
from a fairy tale.
-Why do you think I'm like a princess?
-Because you're pretty.
My mom always calls me "princess"
because I'm pretty.
Ma'am, how about a photo?
My goodness, thank you.
Go stand next to her.
Come here.
You're not my fan, are you?
Pardon?
In all my fairy tales,
the witch is always the one that's pretty.
Who told you all princesses
are kind and pretty?
Did your mom tell you that?
Princess, look over here.
If you really want to be that pretty,
I want you to say this.
-One.
-"Mom.
-I'm going to be...
-Two.
a pretty witch."
Three.
Princess.
-Oh, goodness.
-Princess!
My gosh.
My gosh. Mun-yeong.
Buongiorno, Mun-yeong.
My gosh, what's with this chain?
What made that little kid cry her eyes out
so early in the morning?
I guess she was touched.
I helped her correct her misconception.
What in the world...
Good job.
It can be very dangerous
for a kid to be biased towards something.
But you helped her fix that?
You really are amazing, Mun-yeong.
Just a second.
OK PSYCHIATRIC HOSPITAL
I don't need your loan. I'm already rich.
Okay, let's get going.
We have about two hours.
So you have time to go to a beauty salon.
Why would I go there?
You can't go there looking like that.
You look like Francesca
who is on her way to a funeral
for the Addams Family.
You can't go to a children's ward
looking like that.
You're not going there to scare the kids.
You're going there to give them hope.
You'll be reading your fairy tale there.
-But you look--
-You said it's dangerous to be biased.
I personally think you're more dangerous.
Mun-yeong, please.
You should dress according to the TPO.
I'll tell them to come to you.
Do you know why I like this restaurant?
-Because the steak--
-No.
The knife here
is amazing.
-Look.
-Mun-yeong, you're bleeding.
How pretty.
I want it.
Good gracious.
Ma'am.
Just a second.
EMPLOYEE CARD CAREGIVER MOON GANG-TAE
Mr. Moon, you need to come to the lounge.
Gosh, that thief ate all my food.
It's as if she's been starving for days.
Ms. Myoung Ji-suk.
Honey.
I feel so empty.
Even so,
you shouldn't eat in such a hurry.
If you do,
you'll get an upset stomach again.
So don't eat everything all at once.
Instead, it'd be great
if you could take your time
to eat your food.
You told me you liked that I ate well.
You took it the wrong way.
It's just that when you like someone,
you even like the way they eat.
Honey.
Then
why did you cheat on me
with that skinny model?
It's okay.
Don't smile at me.
It disgusts me.
-Put your arms up like this.
-Let me go!
Then pull them down like this.
-Stay still!
-I don't belong here!
Let me go! Let go of me!
I can't go in here! I can't!
Let go!
I don't belong here!
-Is he a new patient?
-Let me go!
Two days ago, he overdosed
on alprazolam with his daughter
and came as an emergency patient.
He used to get treated
for his anxiety disorder.
I think he tried
to commit suicide with her.
By the looks of it, I think he wanted to
kill his daughter and then kill himself.
Where's Go-eun?
Where is Go-eun? Where is my daughter?
Fortunately, she threw up
right after she took the drug.
And she's getting counseling for PTSD
at our child psychology department.
Go-eun.
Go-eun, what's on your mind?
Let me go!
He's going to receive
a psychiatric assessment this afternoon.
So check his vitals every hour.
And double-check the restraining band
as you give him an IV fluid.
Okay.
After the reading, you will
answer questions from the audience.
Then you'll give out
your autographed storybooks to the kids.
And you'll be done once you take a photo
with the hospital staff for PR.
I'm not sure if I'm a secretary
or the CEO of a publishing company.
I'm seriously starting to wonder.
I got hired as an art director.
But I had no idea that I'd be
working as your minion.
Hey, you told me you'll do anything
during the interview.
Well, I didn't know
you'd make me do physical labor.
I hired you
knowing that you're not very smart.
What do you want me to do?
Should I just fire you?
No.
OK PSYCHIATRIC HOSPITAL
“OK Psychiatric Hospital”?
Sir, do you get counseling?
That's such a good idea.
Answer the phone.
-Hello?
-Put it on speaker.
Hello? Mr. Lee?
I'm Nam Ju-ri,
a nurse at OK Psychiatric Hospital.
Come this way.
It's so hard to reach you.
You never text us back either.
Are you listening?
Oh, yes. I'm a bit busy--
I believe we told you
that we set a date
for Mr. Ko Dae-hwan's surgery.
How long do we need to wait
for the guardian's consent?
You can't keep
avoiding our calls like this.
That's the same thing
as killing the patient.
Ko Dae-hwan.
He's dead to me.
Why do you keep trying to bring him back
to life? Are you Jesus?
-Excuse me.
-Ju-ri.
If you're so desperate,
come and get the signature yourself.
What's wrong? What is it?
-What happened?
-She wants me to go to her.
Is she out of her mind or what?
If she's not sane, she should come here.
Ms. Park.
Let me hear about his medical history.
The patient in room 203 with dementia.
Oh, Mr. Ko Dae-hwan?
He needs to get surgery
due to his glioblastoma relapse.
But his guardian doesn't care?
This patient has been with us
for the longest period of time.
But his guardian
never once visited or called
which means he's being neglected.
So instead of just
calling his ungrateful guardian,
why don't you actually visit her in person
so that we can save the patient?
What?
Is that really necessary?
You're going to do it, right?
I know you're a professional.
If you let me take the rest of the day
and tomorrow off,
-I'll go see her myself.
-Why do you need two days?
Do you have a boyfriend in Seoul?
I guess you do.
Ju-ri, you have a boyfriend?
No.
Well then, I'll be off soon.
I bet she does have a boyfriend.
She's a traitor.
I don't think your daughter
will be able to come here.
No... No.
What's the matter?
No!
Die.
If she comes...
FAIRY TALE READING
WITH AUTHOR KO MUN-YEONG
Gang-tae.
Yes?
I heard someone puked on you
this afternoon.
-She even slapped me.
-My gosh.
You should make sure
the day doesn't get worse.
Kim Seung-cheol, the patient in isolation,
will be transferred to the police.
Yes, I heard. I'll take care of him.
We had a team dinner last night,
and we made a bet.
"A bet"?
"Why does Moon Gang-tae
move from hospital to hospital every year
instead of settling down?"
We tried to guess the answer.
Number one.
Because you lost all your money,
and you're getting chased by loan sharks.
Number two.
You got yourself in big trouble,
and you're working here
to hide your identity from the cops.
Number three. You always get kicked out
of every hospital you work at
for hitting on the nurses and patients.
Which one did you bet on?
I bet on
number three. Women.
So what's the answer?
Number four.
Men.
Gang-tae. My gosh.
The coffee tastes nice.
-"I'm still going to love you.
-I'm still going to love you.
-You're just as pitiful as I am.
-I'm not pitiful.
-Yes, you are.
-You're even treating me like an orphan?
-Even if you're not,
-you think and act like an orphan."
-you think and act like an orphan.
AUTHOR KO MUN-YEONG'S BEST SELLERS
-"You're thoughtless, insecure,
-You're thoughtless,
-unconscientious,
-insecure, unconscientious,
-and empty-hearted. That's why.
-But I'm still going to love you.
-Do you know why?
-Because I decided to do so."
-Because I decided to do so.
I also decided...
"I'm still going to love you."
Did you eat?
I ate jjamppong. Jjamppong.
Again? You need to stop eating noodles.
I bought you some side dishes yesterday.
-What are you doing?
-I'm drawing.
You're drawing on that woman's book again.
It's not "that woman."
She's writer Ko Mun-yeong.
Yes, Ko Mun-yeong.
She's coming to our hospital today.
She'll be reading her book
to the children at our hospital.
Sang-tae?
I'll go. I'll go there.
I'll go there right now.
I'll take bus number 243, the blue bus,
get off at Jayang three-way intersection,
and take 5413,
-the green bus.
-Sang-tae. No, wait.
Get off at Myungsung University
Medical Center and walk--
Moon Sang-tae!
Take three deep breaths.
Listen to me carefully.
Even if you leave now,
you won't be able to make it on time.
Plus, it's only for the patients
in the children's ward.
But you're not a child, are you?
Moon Sang-tae. 35 years old.
Born in 1984, the year of the rat.
I'm younger than I look,
but I'm not a child.
Exactly. You're an adult.
But instead,
I'll get you an autograph if I can.
Meeting her is just a one-time thing,
but her autograph will last forever.
Now, which one do you think is better?
Her autograph.
Who do you like more? Me or Ko Mun-yeong?
Hello? Sang-tae?
I didn't want to ruin her mood
prior to the big event.
That's why I kept it quiet.
I was going to convince her
and take her there
after she successfully finished
today's reading.
Darn it. I totally messed up.
I'm getting a bad feeling.
Why does Ms. Ko hate her father so much?
She hates everyone apart from herself.
Don't even ask why.
That's just how she was born.
If you want to live a long life,
just stay quiet.
Gosh, where in the world is she?
It's almost time.
Excuse me.
-Can you please--
-This is my last one.
No, I don't want one. Can you put it out?
I just lit it up.
This is a non-smoking area, so put it out.
Do you believe in destiny?
-What?
-You heard me.
Who cares about destiny?
If someone shows up when you need them,
you call that destiny.
THE BOY WHO FED ON NIGHTMARES
Gosh, that was so loud.
Very realistic, isn't it?
She's good at acting, too.
"The boy woke up
from another awful nightmare.
Bad memories from the past
that he wanted to erase from his head
were replayed in his dreams every night
and haunted him nonstop.
The boy was terrified of falling asleep.
So one day,
he went to the witch and begged.
'Please get rid of all my bad memories
so that I won't ever have
a nightmare again.
Then I will do everything you ask.'"
Go-eun!
-Go-eun!
-My goodness, what's wrong with you?
Where is Go-eun?
Go-eun!
Go-eun... Where is Go-eun?
Seagull 777. I repeat. Seagull 777.
A NON-PROVOCATIVE CODE FOR PATIENTS
WHO ESCAPE FROM THEIR WARDS
IN PSYCHIATRIC HOSPITALS
Hello.
And lie on your stomach.
Let's try one more.
-Are you serious?
-Sorry.
He said it was uncomfortable
so I took it off for a bit.
Did you bring the restraint straps?
Oh, I forgot.
Look to your right and hold onto your arm.
Now, let's try it one more time.
"Years went by,
and the boy became an adult.
-He no longer had nightmares.
-Go-eun.
But for some strange reason,
he wasn't happy at all."
-Go-eun.
-What's your problem?
-What's going on?
-Go-eun.
Go-eun.
Gosh, what are you doing?
"One night, a blood moon
filled the night sky,
and the witch finally showed up again
to take what he had promised
in return for granting his wish.
And he shouted at her
with so much resentment.
'All my bad memories are gone.
But why...
Why can't I become happy?'
Then the witch took his soul
as they had promised,
and told him this."
-What's going on?
-Mom!
What the hell is happening?
We unfortunately have to end this here
due to unforeseen circumstances.
All hospital staff and guardians,
please take all children
-back to the children's ward immediately.
-My gosh.
-What's going on?
-Go-eun.
Go-eun.
-This isn't over yet.
-Go-eun.
Kids, it's not over.
-Come on.
-Go on.
-Damn it.
-Gosh.
-Mom!
-Mom, I'm scared.
Okay, let's go.
Hello?
Damn it.
Go up.
-Hey!
-Let's go up.
Wait! Wait up.
Go-eun! My gosh, Go-eun...
Come with Daddy.
-Who are you to abruptly end this?
-No!
-Right before the highlight of the event.
-Let me--
Is it time to wrap up saying,
"to be continued"?
-It's okay. It's all right.
-No, you're scaring me.
Bring the kids back.
Come on. Let's go.
There are only a few lines left,
so they can leave after hearing the rest.
-You should evacuate--
-Now!
Dad, don't be like this.
I'm scared.
Listen to me carefully.
If we get caught here, I'll be locked away
in a mental institution,
and you'll end up in an orphanage.
Will you be okay
if you can never see Daddy again?
I want to live. I don't want to die.
I told you.
Kids can never live on their own.
If we must be separated like this,
we should just die together.
That'd be better.
What the...
That's such bullshit.
You're the first worthless human being
I've encountered in a long time.
Look at that gross, slimy face.
Who are you? Do you have a death wish?
Have you ever killed anyone?
You don't think
you can get on with your life,
yet you can't even muster up the courage
to die alone.
That's why you're trying to lure this kid
into going down that road first.
What?
Don't be such a loser.
Go ahead and take your life alone.
You crazy bitch!
A knife...
Hey!
You piece of...
-Are you all right?
-My dad is...
Hey! Who are you to meddle in my business?
She's my child.
I can kill her if I want to.
I can do whatever I want with her!
Choke me. Choke me harder, you moron.
You lunatic!
Die. Just die!
It'll be quick.
It'll just be a moment.
It'll end even before you know it.
Die. Just die.
-Die!
-Mr. Kim Seung-cheol!
Let go. Get off me!
You piece of...
Come here.
Let go. Let go of me!
Let go, you bastard! I'll kill you all!
-Let go!
-I'm doing this so that you won't be hurt,
so just calm down!
I'll kill you all. I'm going to kill...
THE BOY WHO FED ON NIGHTMARES
So it wasn't destiny
after all.
I'd appreciate it
if you could stay out of this.
Let go of the knife first.
This man is a patient.
No.
He is not a patient.
He's vermin.
What in the world...
She's completely nuts.
She's insane!
That crazy bitch.
I nearly died because of that bitch!
Let go. Let go of me, you idiots.
Get her, not me.
She's the one who needs help!
-Don't lose him.
-Let go, you bastards!
I told you to get
that insane woman in there!
-Let go!
-Gosh, stay still.
Is the knife hurt? Why are you
wrapping that around the knife?
If he's non compos mentis,
we can say I acted in self-defense.
I just wanted to give him a small cut
with the knife,
but you overreacted and hurt yourself.
Here.
Your hand, not the knife.
Here's my special service.
You know what?
In this world,
there are people who deserve to die.
But some thoughtful freaks
kill them for us in secret.
That is why the clueless civilians
can sleep peacefully at night,
completely unaware of it.
Which one do you think I am?
You're
a clueless freak.
Oh, boy.
Thanks to you, my suturing skills
are getting better by the day.
Stop hurting yourself already.
Mr. Moon?
Mr. Moon Gang-tae.
Yes?
What were you thinking about?
It's done.
Okay, fine.
The event turned into total chaos
because of the patient who escaped,
so let's just consider it buzz marketing.
But what about the knife fight?
How are you going to explain it?
You said one of the hospital staff
got hurt.
What if they distribute a press release?
"A famous children's book author
brandished a knife.
Is she working on a martial arts novel?"
You'll see the headlines everywhere.
Just bribe them.
You've done it many times.
What if that doesn't work? What do we do?
We'll use a honey trap. I'll seduce them.
Get in.
You go ahead.
I have to take care of something.
What do you need to do?
Hey, Mun-yeong!
Is she going to cause trouble again?
ADMIN MANAGER
A patient who should have been
in solitary confinement
barged in there and ruined the event.
The guardians are calling to complain,
so the phones are ringing off the hook.
We need to quickly find someone
who will take the bullet.
Are you saying I should be that person?
The one who was in charge
of the transfer is a newbie,
so I can't really fire him.
I see here that you've worked
at so many different hospitals
in the past ten years.
My gosh, 15 hospitals in total.
And less than a year at all of them.
You've been with us for ten months now,
so you'll be quitting soon anyway.
EMPLOYEE CARD CAREGIVER MOON GANG-TAE
Gang-tae.
I'll say you worked here for a year
so that you can get your severance pay.
Let's just sort it out like that.
Hey, it's me.
Get me the contact information of the guy
who got hurt because of Mun-yeong.
What do you think?
I need to bribe him or something
to silence him.
Come on. You know the drill.
JAE-SU'S FRIED CHICKEN DELIVERY
I was delivering an order
but saw a guy sitting here
looking like a sick chicken
and knew it was you.
Hop on. I'll give you a ride.
You freak.
You hurt yourself again?
Damn it.
Is he ignoring my calls?
If he bled, I'm sure he'll sue her.
NURSE NAM JU-RI
Hello, Ms. Nam.
Oh, I see. You're already here?
Right.
The room number is...
Just a moment, please.
Did you order room service?
Where did he go?
Thanks.
Alberto, no. Don't do this to me.
No, Alberto. Don't be like this.
Please, Alberto!
No! Don't do this to me, Alberto!
-Shit.
-What's wrong?
-Gosh!
-What's going on?
Hang on. Alberto... Gosh!
Alberto!
Giddy-up!
Alberto! Shit. Alberto, please...
Don't die.
Gang-tae!
I'm really okay.
Your brother must be waiting for you,
so just take a cab home!
I won't say that you ditched me!
I totally understand!
Because that is
what a true loyal friend would do!
Shut it and just keep on pulling.
ANOTHER LONG DAY, RIGHT? CHEER UP!
YOU WILL MEET YOUR SOUL MATE SOON.
You've changed so much.
I almost couldn't recognize you
because you no longer look like a hick.
Has it been almost 20 years
since I transferred to a different school?
Yes.
We just need your signature here.
The doctor must've already
explained everything over the phone.
You should actually do this in person--
Hey, you traveled for three hours
just to get my signature
on this stupid paperwork?
Do you have a strong sense of duty?
Or are you just a do-gooder?
Our hospital is a psychiatric clinic,
so we have to work with another hospital
to perform surgery.
-In your father's case--
-I told you that he's dead.
I'm an orphan. You know that.
But your mother is alive--
I registered her death a long time ago.
Do you want to hear something interesting?
My dad's soul is dead,
but he's physically alive like a zombie.
As for my mom,
she physically died many years ago.
However,
her soul is still alive.
So between the two of them,
who's really dead?
Tell me, nurse.
Which one of them is really dead?
Your father...
I mean, Mr. Ko Dae-hwan.
He may end up in critical condition
if he doesn't undergo surgery this time.
His cognitive functions--
Hey, others will think
that you're his daughter.
Oh, why don't we do that?
You can be Ko Dae-hwan's daughter.
I'll be your mom's daughter.
I'll sign this consent form
if you agree to that.
What do you say?
Your mom is a good cook.
Shall I come over for some food
like the good old days?
I see that you still don't get my jokes.
You're no fun.
She pisses me off.
She's insane.
I can't believe she writes
children's literature.
That's bizarre.
No, she's not "insane."
She was just born that way.
Goodness. Can you diagnose people
at a glance
now that you've worked
at mental hospitals for ten years?
Stop overreacting.
You fool, can you please learn
to overreact a little?
You got fired with a knife injury
because of those lunatics.
I can't believe you just left.
-You should've caused a scene.
-Had I done that,
it would've felt nice,
-but I wouldn't get my severance pay.
-Well done.
Your brother got expelled from school,
and you got fired from work.
You guys are two peas in a pod.
It was about time I quit anyway.
It's this time of the year.
When the night breeze feels warm.
I guess
butterflies will appear soon.
Right.
How's Sang-tae? No signs yet?
No, not yet.
Then where should we go next?
-Should we go to another country?
-Do you even have a passport?
Sang-tae should learn English.
Jae-su.
Don't say anything to my brother.
Gosh, you only care about your brother.
I'm sick of this.
I'm so jealous.
You scared me.
What's wrong?
Did that woman also hit you in the head?
The autograph.
I forgot to get her autograph.
-I promised him I'd get it.
-She must've hit you hard in the head.
What do I do, Jae-su?
Oh, dear.
AUTHOR KO MUN-YEONG'S AUTOGRAPH
THE BOY WHO FED ON NIGHTMARES
Gosh, her autograph
looks like a bunch of heroglyphs.
Hieroglyphs, not "heroglyphs."
Hurry up. Sang-tae is waiting.
Done. Have a look.
Hey, look. It's very similar, isn't it?
Nice job, Jae-su!
Hey, quiet down.
-Happy now?
-Yes.
This will make Sang-tae happy.
Don't smile like that, dude.
It disgusts me.
A patient said the same thing to me
earlier today.
Is my smile that annoying?
You don't know?
You really don't know?
What?
When you smile,
you look like the Joker.
With those sad eyes and the corners
of your lips pointing up like this.
Look in the mirror. You'll see.
Come on, let's go.
Sang-tae, I'm home.
This...
This is fake. It's fake.
-No, it's her real autograph. It's--
-This is fake.
-Gosh, that's...
-Sang-tae, wait.
-This is fake.
-Gosh, that... Goodness.
This is fake, fake, fake. It's all fake.
You lied to me.
-Sang-tae, I'm sorry.
-You lied to me.
You lied to me?
-Lying is bad.
-Sang-tae, I was too busy today that...
Lying is bad. You lied to me?
Even little kids know
that it's wrong to lie.
-Shall we go to the bookstore tomorrow?
-You lied?
-Even three-year-olds--
-Shall we get the dinosaur encyclopedia?
-What?
-You always wanted that book.
-Sang-tae?
-You lied?
You lied? Why did you lie to me?
-Lying is bad.
-Gosh, you poor thing.
This is all Ko Mun-yeong's fault.
I'm going to burn all these books!
What is this?
-Why would a boy feed on nightmares?
-No!
-No, don't.
-I'll burn all these books.
-No, you can't!
-Look, I'll...
-No!
-No? Why not?
-It's mine. Don't do this.
-No, I'll burn them all.
-Hello.
-Let go.
I am Lee Sang-in,
the CEO of SangSangESang Publishers,
a children's book publisher.
First of all,
I'd like to sincerely apologize
for the unfortunate incident
between you and our author earlier today.
I'd like to speak with you
if you can spare a moment
out of your busy schedule.
It'd be greatly appreciated
if you could stop by our office tomorrow.
Please don't say no.
I'd really like to meet you. Please.
-Please!
-Why would you read children's books?
You don't understand art.
Art is such a beautiful thing.
What do you mean I don't understand art?
Art is...
Naughty erotica books are what I call art.
-This is...
-Go away. Just go home.
-Just leave.
-Come on, Sang-tae. I like you so much.
Of course. I knew it. Let's see.
Sure.
"Sure"?
Gosh, that doesn't sound good.
Around 6 p.m. today
at a hospital in Seoul,
-a man who was supposed
-I'm getting
-to be transferred to the police
-a bad feeling about this.
after attempting to take his own life
as well as his daughter's
was found dead in solitary confinement.
The police are investigating his death
at the moment.
It is said that he caused a scene
at a book reading event
which was organized
for pediatric patients in the hospital,
but the security guards
were able to stop him immediately.
He has such beautiful eyes.
Do you know this?
In this world,
there are people who deserve to die.
But some thoughtful freaks
kill them for us in secret.
That is why the clueless civilians
can sleep peacefully at night,
completely unaware of it.
What the...
I told you not to look down on me.
Yes, I won't.
-Stop him.
-Okay, go back to sleep.
JAE-SU IS NOT ALLOWED!
THE BOY WHO FED ON NIGHTMARES
"The boy woke up
from another awful nightmare.
Bad memories from the past
that he wanted to erase from his head
were replayed in his dreams every night
and haunted him nonstop.
Years went by,
and the boy became an adult.
He no longer had nightmares.
But for some strange reason,
he wasn't happy at all.
One night, a blood moon
filled the night sky,
and the witch finally showed up again
to take what he had promised
in return for granting his wish.
And he shouted at her
with so much resentment.
'All my bad memories are gone. But why...
Why can't I become happy?'
Then the witch took his soul
as they had promised
and told him this.
'Hurtful, painful memories.
Memories of deep regrets.
Memories of hurting others and being hurt.
Memories of being abandoned.
Only those with such memories
buried in their hearts
can become stronger, more passionate,
and emotionally flexible.
And only those can attain happiness.'"
THE BOY WHO FED ON NIGHTMARES
Never forget today.
You can't fall asleep?
Where's my dad?
Everything will be okay. Don't worry.
Will the police
take him?
Will he be locked away
in a mental institution?
Are you scared that
he'll show up again and harass you?
That won't happen again.
My dad...
My dad is
not a bad person.
He's just not well.
He's mentally ill.
So please...
Don't let the police take him.
Please allow me to live with him.
I want to live with my dad.
I want to live with him.
I miss my dad.
-"So don't forget any of it.
-Dad...
Remember it all and overcome it.
If you don't overcome it,
you'll always be a kid
whose soul never grows."
THE BOY WHO FED ON NIGHTMARES
What? Butterflies...
No, those butterflies!
-What? What's going on?
-Butterflies!
-Goodness.
-What's the matter?
-Those butterflies...
-Sang-tae.
-Butterflies...
Gosh, those butterflies...
Butterflies! Those butterflies!
-Don't! I'm sorry!
-They're back.
-Don't...
-Those damn butterflies.
Those butterflies!
They said they'll kill me.
The butterflies will kill me!
They're coming to kill me!
-I have to run away.
-Sang-tae.
I have to go. I must run away!
Go away!
Hey, Gang-tae!
It's not even the peak moving season.
Why move out?
Gosh, I can't believe this.
Gang-tae!
You still have months left on your lease.
Why would you want to...
Gosh, you scared me.
Mister, you slept here again?
Then you need to chip in
for the water usage!
Go bring the young man.
We're friends. Why are you talking
as if he's much younger than me?
Cut it out. Where is he?
I wonder too.
Where on earth did he go so early?
Mr. Moon Gang-tae?
Hello.
My boss is on his way back
from the print shop now.
He said he'll be about ten minutes late.
NO PARKING
RESERVED FOR CEO
This way.
Please wait here for a moment.
Sure.
THE HAND, THE MONKFISH
AUTHOR KO MUN-YEONG
Guys, she's here! Clear your desks.
Tidy up.
Hurry.
Who sits here?
The accounting manager. Why do you ask?
This is pretty.
-I want this.
-Then you can have it.
I was going to anyway.
Ms. Ko, what brings you by?
Zombie Kid is coming out today.
-Where's Mr. Lee?
-Well...
What a sight.
You look dashing in your regular clothes.
Like an escort who's here to harass me
to pay off my tab.
I thought you'd be different,
but I was obviously wrong.
How much did he offer you?
If you can't talk politely,
at least try not to be so cryptic.
And look at you talking to me so casually.
I practically stabbed you.
-What about it?
-How much did Mr. Lee offer you
to compensate you for that
as well as to make sure
you won't tell anyone about it?
I guess this method has always worked.
Verbal consolation is useless.
Money is the best.
Not to me.
Then what do you want? Sex?
Is it worth more than money?
Then why are you here?
If not for money or sex,
what are you here for?
I was hoping
I could see you again.
That's why I'm here.
Your eyes.
I wanted to see them again.
My eyes?
Your eyes
remind me of someone I used to know.
Who is that person?
Someone who's messed up
and has no conscience.
A woman
whose eyes
completely lacked warmth.
That woman...
Were you afraid of her?
No, the opposite.
I liked
her.
Sub by ®NETFLIX
It's Okay To Not Be Okay - tvN
Synced by ParkMinYoung℠
Are you that excited?
"Dear Sang-tae!
I hope you can come
to my book launch party."
It's boring to say that
we're destined for each other.
I thought I was on the run
Don't touch my hair!
because of my brother.
Coward.
Where is Ko Mun-yeong?
You won't end up well
if you get involved with her.
Don't go.
I want you to be my safety pin.
Keep me under control
so that I won't explode.
Subtitle translation by Liya Choi